<topics ir-datasets-id="iranthology-memory">
 <topic number="1">
  <query>
   Deep Neural Networks
  </query>
  <original_query>
   <query_id>
    1
   </query_id>
   <title>
    Deep Neural Networks
   </title>
   <description>
    Which papers talk about Deep Neural Networks?
   </description>
   <narrative>
    Relevant papers have at least one mention of Deep Neural. Paper containing only Deep or Neural are not relevant.
   </narrative>
  </original_query>
 </topic>
 <topic number="2">
  <query>
   Information Retrieval
  </query>
  <original_query>
   <query_id>
    2
   </query_id>
   <title>
    Information Retrieval
   </title>
   <description>
    Which papers talk about Information Retrieval?
   </description>
   <narrative>
    Relevant paper have at least one mention of Information Retrieval. Paper containing only Information or Retrieval are not relevant.
   </narrative>
  </original_query>
 </topic>
 <topic number="3">
  <query>
   Analysis for Android apps
  </query>
  <original_query>
   <query_id>
    3
   </query_id>
   <title>
    Analysis for Android apps
   </title>
   <description>
    Which papers talk about the analysis of android apps?
   </description>
   <narrative>
    Relevant papers talk at least in one line about android apps. Paper containing only apps are not relevant.
   </narrative>
  </original_query>
 </topic>
 <topic number="4">
  <query>
   The University of Amsterdam
  </query>
  <original_query>
   <query_id>
    4
   </query_id>
   <title>
    The University of Amsterdam
   </title>
   <description>
    Which papers are created by the University of Amsterdam?
   </description>
   <narrative>
    Relevant papers are created or at least co-written by the University of Amsterdam. Paper containing only
      University not relevant.
   </narrative>
  </original_query>
 </topic>
 <topic number="5">
  <query>
   Neural Ranking for eCommerce Product Search
  </query>
  <original_query>
   <query_id>
    5
   </query_id>
   <title>
    Neural Ranking for eCommerce Product Search
   </title>
   <description>
    Which paper is about Ranking Product Search and its applications in eCommerce?
   </description>
   <narrative>
    Relevant papers that addresses application of Task Models and Textual Embeddings in the field of electronic
      commerce. Not relevant are papers showcasing applications that do not contain the topic eCommerce.
   </narrative>
  </original_query>
 </topic>
 <topic number="6">
  <query>
   web pages evolution
  </query>
  <original_query>
   <query_id>
    6
   </query_id>
   <title>
    web pages evolution
   </title>
   <description>
    Which paper is about the evolution of web pages?
   </description>
   <narrative>
    Relevant paper have at least one mention of web evolution. Paper containing only web page or evolution are not relevant.
   </narrative>
  </original_query>
 </topic>
</topics>